uniontelecard.com 2006-06-15

# IDT Corporation - Privacy Policy

|  |   
---  
   
IDT's Privacy Policy - Generally 

IDT is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This IDT Privacy Policy applies to IDT's family of Web sites and governs data collection and usage at all IDT sites and services. Please read the complete IDT Privacy Policy below.

The purpose of the IDT Web sites' privacy policy is to inform you, as a welcome visitor to our Web sites, about the kinds of information we may gather about you when you visit our Web sites, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and your ability to correct the information. Finally, please note that this policy applies only to IDT Web sites and Web sites that carry the IDT Web sites' brand, and not to other companies' or organizations' Web sites to which we link. We have clearly marked IDT Web sites and these branded Web sites with our logo so you know where this policy applies. 

Information About All IDT Web sites' Visitors

IDT keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within the Web sites, in order to determine what sites and services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within IDT to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area. Our service automatically gathers certain usage information like the numbers and frequency of visitors to IDT Web sites and its areas. This is similar to the way television ratings tell the networks how many people tuned in to a program. We only use such data in the aggregate. This collective data helps us determine how much our customers use parts of the site, so we can improve our site to assure that it is as appealing as we can make it for as many of you as possible. 

For example, IDT Web sites may use a technology nicknamed "cookies" that tells us how and when pages in our site are visited, and by how many people. IDT cookies do not collect personally identifiable information and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personally identifiable information to tell us who you are or even what your screen name or e-mail address is. We also may provide statistical "ratings" information, never information about you personally, to our IDT Web sites partners about how our members, collectively, use IDT Web sites. We do this so they too can understand how much people use their areas and our site in order for them to provide you with the best possible Web experience as well. 

Use of Cookies

Some IDT Web sites may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize IDT's pages, or register with IDT sites or services, a cookie helps IDT to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same IDT Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the IDT features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the IDT services or Web sites you visit. 

Use of Third Party Advertising

The majority of the advertisements you see on IDT Web sites are displayed by IDT. In addition, IDT also allows other companies, called third-party advertisers, to display advertisements while you are viewing content on IDT Web sites. These advertisement are selected based on what we believe will be of most interest to you. 

Information About You 

Sometimes, we may specifically ask for information about you when you sign up to use a service or when you order a product. IDT does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. We do, however, need certain information -- such as name, age, Internet address or screen name, billing address, type of computer, credit card number -- in order to provide that service or product to you. We may also use that information to let you know of additional products and services about which you might be interested. You can choose not to receive such information if you don't want to by letting us know on the registration screen when you sign up for the product or service. We may ask you for information about your interests so that both you and we can take advantage of the interactivity of the online medium, but you may always choose to respond or not. Additionally, we may provide you with an opportunity to be listed in a directory on one of our IDT- branded services -- these listings are also optional and you can make changes to or eliminate this information when you want to. 

IDT does not associate sensitive data, such as your race, religion, or political affiliations, with personally identifiable information. IDT takes precautions to segregate any sensitive data you may provide on IDT sites and services that reference your race, religion, sexual orientation, ethnicity or political affiliations. 

Security of your Personal Information

IDT secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. IDT secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites through the use of Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encrypted protection. 

Third Party Disclosure 

We do not use or disclose information about your individual visits to IDT Web sites or information that you may give us, such as your name, address, email address or telephone number, to any outside companies. However, we may share with our Web site partners aggregated statistical "ratings" information about the use of IDT Web sites. IDT may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to IDT, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

IDT Web sites will never disclose your personal information without notice unless it is required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:  
(a) conform to the law or comply with legal process served on IDT or the site;  
(b) protect and defend the rights or property of IDT, an IDT Web site; and,  
(c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of IDT, its Web sites, or the public. 

Children On The Web 

IDT Corporation, Inc. takes special care to protect the safety and privacy of children using our services. We do not specifically collect information about children and believe that children should get their parents' consent before giving out any personal information. We encourage you to participate in your child's experience in cyberspace and to review our important safety tips before your child explores the Internet. We also encourage you and your child to visit IDT Web sites that provides access to age-appropriate content available on the Web. IDT also recommends that parents use Web filtering technology to supervise their kids' access to the Web. 

IDT Web sites Privacy Policy Changes

IDT will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect company and customer feedback. When IDT posts changes to this Statement, you will see the word "updated" next to the Privacy Statement link on the front page of IDT. If there are material changes to this Statement or in how IDT will use your personally identifiable information, IDT will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. IDT encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how IDT is protecting your information. 

Enforcement

By upholding our commitment to protecting the privacy of your personal information, IDT has agreed to disclose its information practices. IDT welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you believe that IDT has not adhered to this Statement, please contact IDT by telephone or postal mail.

IDT Corporation

520 Broad Street

Newark, New Jersey 07102

(973) 438-4167

RULES OF USER CONDUCT

By posting information in or otherwise using any communications service, chat room, virtual television channel, message board, newsgroup, software library, or other interactive service that may be available to you on or through our Web sites, you agree that you will not upload, post, or otherwise distribute or facilitate distribution of any content -- including text, communications, software, images, sounds, data, or other information \-- that:

\- is unlawful, threatening, abusive, harassing, defamatory, libelous, deceptive, fraudulent, invasive of another's privacy, tortious, contains explicit or graphic descriptions or accounts of sexual acts (including but not limited to sexual language of a violent or threatening nature directed at another individual or group of individuals), or otherwise violates IDT Corporation's rules or policies;   
\- victimizes, harasses, degrades, or intimidates an individual or group of individuals on the basis of religion, gender, sexual orientation, race, ethnicity, age, or disability;   
\- infringes on any patent, trademark, trade secret, copyright, right of publicity, or other proprietary right of any party;   
\- constitutes unauthorized or unsolicited advertising, junk or bulk e-mail (also known as "spamming"), chain letters, any other form of unauthorized solicitation, or any form of lottery or gambling;   
\- contains software viruses or any other computer code, files, or programs that are designed or intended to disrupt, damage, or limit the functioning of any software, hardware, or telecommunications equipment or to damage or obtain unauthorized access to any data or other information of any third party; or   
impersonates any person or entity, including any employee or representative of IDT Corporation.   
You also agree that you will not harvest or collect information about the users or members of the IDT Web Sites or use such information for the purpose of transmitting or facilitating transmission of unsolicited bulk electronic e-mail or communications.

You further agree that you will not knowingly solicit or collect personal information from a child 12 years old or younger without appropriate prior verifiable parental consent.

IDT Corporation generally does not pre-screen, monitor, or edit the content posted by users of communications services, chat rooms, message boards, newsgroups, software libraries, or other interactive services that may be available on or through the IDT Web Sites. However, IDT Corporation and its agents have the right at their sole discretion to remove any content that, in IDT Corporation's judgment, does not comply with the Rules of User Conduct or is otherwise harmful, objectionable, or inaccurate. IDT Corporation is not responsible for any failure or delay in removing such content. 

REQUESTING PERMISSION TO USE COPYRIGHTED MATERIALS

The IDT Web Sites contain various types of materials (including product information, files, articles, movies, cartoons, and other digital entertainment), photos, icons, and other copyrighted materials owned by us or our Content Providers. You may not use this information in any manner or for any purpose other than as expressly authorized in the IDT Web Sites. The following information applies only to materials we own. You must contact the copyright owner directly for permission to use third party materials displayed on the IDT Web Sites. 

Do I Need Permission?

You are authorized to view, copy, download, and print for personal use only any copyrighted materials we own that are available on this web site, subject to the following conditions: 

The documents may be used solely for personal, noncommercial, and informational purposes. They may not be posted or distributed.   
The documents may not be modified.   
All copyright and other proprietary notices must be retained in the document.   
This permission does not extend to materials owned by other content providers that appear on this web site.   
You may not reproduce, copy, or redistribute the design or layout of the IDT Web Sites, individual elements of the Web Site design, or our logos without our express written permission. 

Permission for Commercial Use

Reproduction, copying, or redistribution for commercial purposes of any materials or design elements on the IDT Web Sites is strictly prohibited without our express written permission. Permission is granted only when certain limited criteria are met.

To request such permission please send email to IDTLegal@corp.idt.net.

Please identify the requested material and the Web Site on which it is found in the subject line, e.g. "Idt.net home page screenshot" or a "Screenshot of our Web Site in Netscape or Explorer browser frame." Include all of the following information in the body of the message:

The content you wish to use and the URL where it is located.   
Where and how it will be used (for example, in an Internet use manual, in a newsletter, or in a movie).   
Where and how copies will be distributed and to what audience.   
How many copies will be produced and distributed.   
When you intend to publish, and your deadline for a response (no shorter than 1 week please).   
Other materials that will be associated with our content.   
Your name, title, company, address, email address, and phone number.   
In addition, please provide an example or mockup of the intended use, either by sending a file attached to your email (in a format readable with a PC), or by fax to (973) 438-1455. We will need all of the above in order to evaluate your request. Please expect 7 to 10 days for processing all requests.

We reserve the right to refuse permission to copy, distribute, broadcast, or publish any of our copyrighted material.

Thank you for your cooperation. Procedure for Making Claims of Copyright Infringement

IDT Corporation, Inc., its subsidiaries, and affiliate companies respect the intellectual property of others, and we ask our Content Providers and those posting materials to the IDT Web Sites to do the same. If you believe that your copyrighted work has been copied and is accessible on the IDT Web Sites in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, please let us know right away by providing our copyright agent with the following information:

\- the electronic or physical signature of the owner of the copyright or the person authorized to act on the owner's behalf.   
\- a description of the copyrighted work that you claim has been infringed and a description of the infringing activity.   
\- identification of the location where the original or an authorized copy of the copyrighted work exists, for example the URL of the Web Site where it is posted or the name of the book in which it has been published.   
\- identification of the URL or other specific location on the IDT Web Sites where the material that you claim is infringing is located; you must include enough information to allow us to locate the material.   
\- your name, address, telephone number, and email address.   
\- a statement by you that you have a good faith belief that the disputed use is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law.   
\- a statement by you, made under penalty of perjury, that the above information in your Notice is accurate and that you are the copyright owner or are authorized to act on the copyright owner's behalf.   
Our agent for notice of claims of copyright infringement on the IDT Web Sites can be reached as follows:

By Mail:

Ely Tendler  
Chief Legal Officer  
IDT Corporation  
520 Broad Street  
Newark, NJ 07102

By phone:

(973) 438-1000  

Copyright Notice

This contact information is only for reporting copyright infringement. Contact information for other matters is provided elsewhere on the IDT Web Sites.

|  |   
---
